Zen yatta is here
tell me your thoughts my friend will we
it is good to fight alongside one of my
brightest pupils and you master
does the suffering of the AMEX here
trouble you master it does my brother
man Dada gave much to improve their
lives but it was not to be
I sense within you the same rage that
once consumed your brother we are
nothing alike
do you have any dreams my friend I do
not dream as humans do but it is my
desire to become the hero if he believes
that I am
it's an honor to me a member of the
Shambhala Monde data was an inspiration
to me to us all
I miss him greatly
I'll have my eye on you on Nick and I
will watch your back in turn
I away in this round Kenji
the master still has a few tricks
being eager to learn is not the same as
learning hatred is not strategy those
who think they are all-knowing know
nothing of what they do not
Khaos baguettes more chaos
move too quickly and you overlook much
revenge is not justice
justice is defined by the hand that
claims it
well done Genji we walk in harmony my
student
I know the doubts that plague you we are
as one my sister
you have much to learn
we walk in the shadows my apprentice